Hyungrok Kim

https://rokrokss.com

: https://github.com/q0115643

t: +821089595643

e: hyungrok.kim@kaist.ac.kr

PROFILE

Currently working for PUBG as a frontend developer.

Belonged in Industrial Design department for 2 years, moved to Computer Science 2 years ago. Studied Data Science and NLP trying to understand the linguistic communication of emotions. Believes firmly that I will relish working as a web developer and serve people with better lives.

WORK EXPERIENCES

PUBG

Frontend Developer

Jul 2019 - Present

Seoul, Republic of Korea

UILAB(http://uilab.kr/)

Undergraduate Researcher

Study on Metaphor Comperhension

Jul 2018 - Dec 2018

Dajeon, Republic of Korea

ORGANIZATION

Korea Design Membership(http://kidp.or.kr)

Attend various design classes

Mar 2016 - Feb 2018

EDUCATION

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology

B.S. in Computer Science Minor in Industrial Design

Mar 2014 - Present

Daejeon, Korea

CORSEWORKS

CS Major

CS574 Natural Language Processing

CS570 Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning

CS492 Introduction to Machine Learning

CS474 Text Mining

CS470 Introduction to Artificial Intelligence

CS330 Operating Systems and Lab

CS320 Programming Language

CS311 Computer Organization CS300 Introduction to Algorithms

CS230 System Programming

CS206 Data Structure

CS204 Discrete Mathematics

Others

ID307 Interface Design

ID220 Interaction Prototyping

ID302 Space Design

ID301 Product Design Factors

ID219 Computer-Aided Design

ID214 Digital Design Graphics ID213 Product Design Fundamentals

ID212 Three-Dimensional Design

ID217 Presentation Technique

ID218 Photo Techniques

ID215 Introduction to Industrial Design

MAS109 Introduction to Linear Algebra MAS205 Probability and Statistics

PROJECTS

REST Countries

https://naranara.net

Simple react webpage of listing various country information.

React, Redux, Typescript, Webpack, Babel, Sass May 2019

Arithmetic Hash



Build LSTM-based query encoder designed to replace the hash algorithm of p2p network

Pytorch, RNN, Markov Model Jan 2019



GCN-RNNG based Korean NMT

Syntax-Aware Model for Neural Machine Translation with Morpheme Structure in Korean

Pytorch, SyntaxNet, GCN, RNNG, KoNLPy, Word2Vec May 2018 - Aug 2018

Neural Poetry Scansion





Based on Original Paper (Proceedings of AAAI 2016) deep-learning apporach to improve performance on poety-analysis

Pytorch, BiLSTM-CRF, Word2Vec

May 2018 - Aug 2018

HarmonyTable



Hardware project of combining harmony & turntable in Interaction Prototyping

Arduino

Sep 2016 - Oct 2016

FlyDuck





Tangible Interface Game

Processing, Arduino

Nov 2016 - Dec 2016